
Git development with Fork on Windows
This is a step-by-step tutorial on how to manage your site’s source code by using Fork on Windows. Fork is a fast and simple git client for Mac and Windows, and Presslabs friendly, too.

In this tutorial, we will show you how to easily set up and make changes to your site’s source code using Fork, an open-source git client for Mac and Windows, which you can download here .

After installing the app, you will be asked to configure the User Name and the email that will be associated with your commits, as well as the Default source folder, which is the default folder where the repositories you clone will be stored.

Fork interface on Windows

Clone your repository
Each site hosted by Presslabs has a git repository associated with it, containing your site’s source code, along with all the changes that have been made along the way. For more details, check our git specifications .

Additionally, we offer free development sites for development, so you should have at least one development site. This can be set up in two ways, so please check out our Development guidlines for insights regarding your development life cycle, depending on your development site setup.